1 General Description
	SC95F8617B/8616B/8615B/8613B/8612B (hereinafter referred to as the SC95F861XB) is a series of enhanced 1T 8051 core industry-standard Flash Microcontroller  unit (MCU) with integrated TouchKey  function, the instruction set is compatible with the standard 8051 series.
	The SC95F861XB has a Super-high-speed 1T 8051 CPU core with an operating frequency of up to 32 MHz.
	The SC95F861X integrates a hardware multiplier and divider hardware CRC and dual DPTR data pointers to accelerate data operations and movement speed. The hardware multiplier and divider and hardware CRC does not occupy CPU cycles, and the operation is implemented by hardware, and the speed is faster than the multiplication and division speed realized by software; dual DPTR data pointers can be used to accelerate data storage and movement.
	The SC95F861XB has high performance and reliability, with a wide operating voltage of 2.0V~5.5V, a super-wide operating temperature of -40°C to 105°C, and has good ESD performance and EFT anti-interference ability. Using the industry-leading eFlash process, the Flash can be written more than 100,000 times, and can be stored for 100 years at room temperature.
	The SC95F861XB has a built-in low power consumption WDT Watchdog Timer. It has a 4-level selectable voltage LVR low voltage reset function and a system clock monitoring function. It has low power consumption capability in operation and power-down modes. Under normal operating mode: about 6mA@32M at 5V.
	The SC95F861XB series is also integrated with super rich hardware resources: built-in 31-channel (high sensitivity) touchkey circuits, 64 KbytesFlash ROM, SRAM: internal 256 bytes+ external 8 Kbytes+ PWM&LCD 80 bytes、6	Kbytes EEPROM,; up to 46 GP I/O (partially gradable control), 16 IO can be externally interrupted, 5 16-bit timers, 14-channel 16-bit PWM:8-channel multi-function dead zone complementary PWM,6 channel PWM output of timer,1 UART,6 USCI(UART/SPI/IIC), Built-in LCD/LED hardware driver, internal ±2% high-precision high- frequency 32/16/8/4 MHz oscillator and ±4% precision low-frequency 32 kHz oscillator, external 32.768 kHz resources such as crystal oscillators. 1 analog comparator, 17 channels 12-bit high precision ADC.
	The SC95F861XB is very convenient for development and debugging, with ISP (In-System Programming), ICP (In-Circuit Programming) and IAP (In-Application Programming). Allow the chip to debug and upgrade the program memory directly on the circuit board when the chip is online or powered.
	The SC95F861XB has very excellent anti-jamming performance and excellent touchkey performance. It is very suitable for various applications about touchkey and main contral system, such as Intelligent home appliances and Intelligent House System, Internet of things, wireless communication, game consoles and other industrial controls, and Consumer application areas.

2 Features
Operating Conditions
	Voltage Range: 2.0V~5.5V
	Temperature Range: -40℃ ~ +105℃
EMS
	ESD
		HBM：MIL-STD-883J Class 3A
		MM：JEDEC EIA/JESD22-A115 Class C
		CDM：ANSI/ESDA/JEDEC JS-002-2018 Class C3
	EFT
		EN61000-4-4 Level 4
Package
	20 PIN: SOP20 / TSSOP20
	28 PIN: SOP28 / TSSOP28
	32 PIN: LQFP32 (7X7)
	44 PIN: LQFP44 (10X10)
	48 PIN: LQFP48 (7X7)
CPU
	Super-high-speed 1T 8051 core
	The instruction set compatible with 8051
	The execution speed is about twice that of other 1T 8051
	Double data pointers (DPTRs)
	Flash ROM64 Kbytes Flash ROM
	MOVC disables addressing 0000H ~ 00FFH
	Can be rewritten 100,000 times
	APROM area allowed IAP operation in Flash can be set to 0K/1K/2K/All APROM by Code Option.
LDROM
	BootLoader code memory
	LDROM area can be set to 0K/1K/2K/4K by Code Option
EEPROM
	Independent 6 Kbytes EEPROM
	Can be rewritten 100,000 times, has more than 100-year preservation life in the ambient temperature of 25℃
SRAM
	256 bytes on-chip direct access RAM
	8 Kbytes on-chip Indirect access RAM
	80 bytes PWM&LCD RAM
Flash Programming and Emulation
	2-wire JTAG programming and emulation interface
System clock (fSYS)
	Built-in high frequency 32 MHz oscillator (fHRC)
		can be selected and set by the programmer as: 32/16/8/4 MHz@2.0~5.5V
		Frequency Error: Within ±1% @ -40 ~ 85℃ @ 2.0 ~ 5.5V
		Frequency Error: Within ±2% @ -40 ~ 105℃ @ 2.0 ~ 5.5V
		The system clock can be automatically calibrated by 32.768 kHz external crystal oscillator, after calibration HRC accuracy can be infinitely close to the accuracy of external 32.768 kHz crystal oscillator.
Built-in low-frequency crystal oscillator circuit:
	32.768k oscillator can be connected externally as a Base Timer clock source.
Built-in low-frequency 32 kHz oscillator (LRC):
	used as the clock source for Base Timer and WDT and wake up STOP
	Frequency Error: After the register correction, within ±4% @ -20 ~ 85℃ @ 4.0 ~ 5.5V
Low-voltage Reset (LVR)
	4 options of reset voltage: 4.3/3.7/ 2.9/1.9V,
	the default value can be selected by the Code Option
Interrupts (INT)
	Timer 0~Timer 4, INT0~2, ADC, PWM, UART, USCI0~5, Base Timer, TK, CMP 20 interrupt sources
	External interrupt contains 3 interrupt vectors, 16 interrupt ports. All can set up rising edge, falling edge, dual edge interrupt.
	Two-level interrupt priority capability
Digital Peripheral
	GPIO: Up to 46 bidirectional independently controllable I/O ports
		Independent setting of pull-up resistors
		P0~P3L(P3.0/1/2/3) port source drive capacity is controlled by four levels
		All IO ports have large sink current drive capability (50mA)
	Built-in WDT, optional clock frequency division ratio
	5 Timers: Timer0~4、Timer1、Time2、Timer3 and Timer4
		Time2、Timer3 and Timer4 have Capture function
		Time2、Timer3 and Timer4 each can provide two conventional PWM
	6-channel 16-bit conventional PWM
		Time2、Timer3 and Timer4 each can provide two conventional PWM
	8-channel 16-bit multi-function PWM
		Public cycle and the duty cycle can be set separately
		Complementary PWM waveforms with dead zones can be output
	One independent UART communication port UART0
	Six UART/SPI/TWI communication interfaces (USCI)
		When USCI0 is set to SPI0, the driving capability of the pins corresponding to its signal port will be enhanced
	Built-in CRC check module
	Integrated with 16 * 16-bit hardware Multiplier-Divide Unit (MDU)
LCD/LED driver
	Choose one of two LCD/LED, share registers and IO ports
	8 X 24, 6 X 26, 5 X 27, or 4X 28 segments LED driver
	LED segment port source drive capability is selectable in four levels
	8 X 24, 6 X 26, 5 X 27, or 4X 28 segments LCD driver
Analog Peripheral
	31-channel high sensitivity TouchKey (TK) circuit.
		Applicable to TouchKey sensor, proximity induction and other TouchKey applications featuring high requirements on sensitivity
		Have very strong anti-interference ability which is able to pass 10V dynamic CS test
		Support self-capacitanceand reciprocal- capacitance mode.
		Support low power consumption mode.
		Complete development support: High-flexible touch software library, intelligent software of debugging.
	17-channel 12-bit±2LSB ADC
		Build-in reference voltage of 2.048V, 1.024V and 2.4V
		The ADC reference voltages is optional: VDD, internal 2.048V, internal 1.024V and 2.4V
		1 internal channel can measure the voltage of the power supply
		ADC conversion complete interruption can be set
	1 Analog Comparator
		4-channel input and 1-channel reference voltage input
		16-level optional comparison voltage
Power Saving Mode
	IDLE Mode: can be woken up by any interrupt
STOP Mode: can be woken up by INT0~2, Base Timer TK and CMP.